Tufts Daily UP029
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Tufts Daily, 2018; UP029.039; 103 Digital Object(s)
  - Tufts Daily, 2018 December 03; UP029.039.078.00041 (Box 78, Folder 41)
    LXXVI,55
  - Tufts Daily, 2018 December 04; UP029.039.078.00042 (Box 78, Folder 42)
    LXXVI,56
  - Tufts Daily, 2018 December 05; UP029.039.078.00043 (Box 78, Folder 43)
    LXXVI,57
  - Tufts Daily, 2018 December 06; UP029.039.078.00044 (Box 78, Folder 44)
    LXXVI,58
  - Tufts Daily, 2018 December 07; UP029.004865
    LXXVI,59
  - Tufts Daily, 2018 December 10; UP029.039.078.00045 (Box 78, Folder 45)
    LXXVI,60
- Tufts Daily, 2019; UP029.040; 118 Digital Object(s)
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 January 16; UP029.040.079.00001 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    LXXVII,1
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 January 18; UP029.004902
    LXXVII,2
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 January 22; UP029.040.079.00002 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    LXXVII,3
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 January 24; UP029.004903
    LXXVII,5
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 January 28; UP029.040.079.00003 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 January 30; UP029.040.079.00004 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    LXXVII,6
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 February 01; UP029.004904
    LXXVII,7
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 February 04; UP029.040.079.00005 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    LXXVII,8
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 February 05; UP029.040.079.00006 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    LXXVII,9
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 February 06; UP029.040.079.00007 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    LXXVII,10
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 February 07; UP029.040.079.00008 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    LXXVII,11
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 February 08; UP029.004921
    LXXVII, 12
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 February 11; UP029.040.079.00009 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    LXXVII,13
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 February 12; UP029.040.079.00010 (Box 79, Folder 10)
    LXXVII,14
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 February 13; UP029.040.079.00011 (Box 79, Folder 11)
    LXXVII,15
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 February 14; UP029.004905
    LXXVII,16
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 February 15; UP029.004906
    LXXVII,17
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 February 19; UP029.004907
    LXXVII,18
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 February 20; UP029.040.079.00012 (Box 79, Folder 12)
    LXXVII,19
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 February 21; UP029.040.079.00013 (Box 79, Folder 13)
    LXXVII,20
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 February 22; UP029.004908
    LXXVII,21
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 February 25; UP029.004909
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 February 26; UP029.040.079.00014 (Box 79, Folder 14)
    LXXVII,23
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 February 27; UP029.040.079.00015 (Box 79, Folder 15)
    LXXVII,24
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 February 28; UP029.040.079.00016 (Box 79, Folder 16)
    LXXVII,25
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 March 01; UP029.004910
    LXXVII,26
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 March 04; UP029.040.079.00017 (Box 79, Folder 17)
    LXXVII,28
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 March 05; UP029.040.079.00018 (Box 79, Folder 18)
    LXXVII,29
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 March 06; UP029.040.079.00019 (Box 79, Folder 19)
    LXXVII,30
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 March 07; UP029.040.079.00020 (Box 79, Folder 20)
    LXXVII,31
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 March 08; UP029.004911
    LXXVII,32
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 March 11; UP029.040.079.00021 (Box 79, Folder 21)
    LXXVII,33
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 March 12; UP029.040.079.00022 (Box 79, Folder 22)
    LXXVII,34
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 March 13; UP029.004912
    LXXVII,35
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 March 14; UP029.040.079.00023 (Box 79, Folder 23)
    LXXVII,36
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 March 15; UP029.004913
    LXXVII,37
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 March 25; UP029.040.079.00024 (Box 79, Folder 24)
    LXXVII,38
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 March 26; UP029.004914
    LXXVII,39
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 March 27; UP029.040.079.00025 (Box 79, Folder 25)
    LXXVII,40
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 March 28; UP029.040.079.00026 (Box 79, Folder 26)
    LXXVII,41
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 March 29; UP029.040.079.00027 (Box 79, Folder 27)
    LXXVII,42
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 April 02; UP029.040.079.00028 (Box 79, Folder 28)
    LXXVII,43
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 April 03; UP029.004915
    LXXVII,44
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 April 04; UP029.040.079.00029 (Box 79, Folder 29)
    LXXVII,45
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 April 05; UP029.004916
    LXXVII,46
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 April 08; UP029.040.079.00030 (Box 79, Folder 30)
    LXXVII,47
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 April 09; UP029.040.079.00031 (Box 79, Folder 31)
    LXXVII,48
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 April 10; UP029.004917
    LXXVII,49
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 April 11; UP029.040.079.00032 (Box 79, Folder 32)
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 April 12; UP029.004918
    LXXVII,51
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 April 16; UP029.040.079.00033 (Box 79, Folder 33)
    LXXVII,52
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 April 17; UP029.040.079.00034 (Box 79, Folder 34)
    LXXVII,53
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 April 18; UP029.040.079.00035 (Box 79, Folder 35)
    LXXVII,54
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 April 19; UP029.004919
    LXXVII,55
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 April 22; UP029.040.079.00036 (Box 79, Folder 36)
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 April 23; UP029.040.079.00037 (Box 79, Folder 37)
    LXXVII,56
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 April 24; UP029.040.079.00038 (Box 79, Folder 38)
    LXXVII,57
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 April 25; UP029.004920
    LXXVII,58
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 May 19; UP029.040.079.00039 (Box 79, Folder 39)
    LXXVII,59
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 August 28; UP029.040.080.00001 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    LXXVIII,1
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 September 03; UP029.040.080.00002 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    LXXVIII,2
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 September 05; UP029.004873
    LXXVIII,3
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 September 09; UP029.040.080.00003 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    LXXVIII,4
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 September 11; UP029.040.080.00004 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    LXXVIII,5
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 September 13; UP029.004874
    LXXVIII,6
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 September 16; UP029.040.080.00005 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    LXXVIII,7
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 September 17; UP029.040.080.00006 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    LXXVIII,8
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 September 18; UP029.040.080.00007 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    LXXVIII,9
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 September 19; UP029.040.080.00008 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    LXXVIII,10
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 September 20; UP029.004875
    LXXVIII,11
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 September 23; UP029.040.080.00009 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    LXXVIII,12
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 September 24; UP029.040.080.00010 (Box 80, Folder 10)
    LXXVIII,13
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 September 25; UP029.040.080.00011 (Box 80, Folder 11)
    LXXVIII,14
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 September 26; UP029.040.080.00012 (Box 80, Folder 12)
    LXXVIII,15
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 September 27; UP029.004876
    LXXVIII,16
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 September 30; UP029.040.080.00013 (Box 80, Folder 13)
    LXXVIII,17
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 October 01; UP029.040.080.00014 (Box 80, Folder 14)
    LXXVIII,18
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 October 02; UP029.004877
    LXXVIII,19
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 October 03; UP029.040.080.00015 (Box 80, Folder 15)
    LXXVIII,20
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 October 04; UP029.004878
    LXXVIII,21
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 October 07; UP029.040.080.00016 (Box 80, Folder 16)
    LXXVIII,22
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 October 08; UP029.040.080.00017 (Box 80, Folder 17)
    LXXVIII,23
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 October 09; UP029.040.080.00018 (Box 80, Folder 18)
    LXXVIII,24
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 October 10; UP029.040.080.00019 (Box 80, Folder 19)
    LXXVIII,25
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 October 11; UP029.004879
    LXXVIII,26
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 October 15; UP029.040.080.00020 (Box 80, Folder 20)
    LXXVIII,27
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 October 16; UP029.004880
    LXXVIII,28
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 October 17; UP029.040.080.00021 (Box 80, Folder 21)
    LXXVIII,29
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 October 18; UP029.004881
    LXXVIII,30
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 October 21; UP029.040.080.00022 (Box 80, Folder 22)
    LXXVIII,31
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 October 22; UP029.040.080.00023 (Box 80, Folder 23)
    LXXVIII,32
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 October 23; UP029.040.080.00024 (Box 80, Folder 24)
    LXXVIII,33
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 October 24; UP029.040.080.00025 (Box 80, Folder 25)
    LXXVIII,34
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 October 25; UP029.004882
    LXXVIII,35
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 October 28; UP029.040.080.00026 (Box 80, Folder 26)
    LXXVIII,36
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 October 29; UP029.040.080.00027 (Box 80, Folder 27)
    LXXVIII,37
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 October 30; UP029.040.080.00028 (Box 80, Folder 28)
    LXXVIII,38
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 October 31; UP029.040.080.00029 (Box 80, Folder 29)
    LXXVIII,
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 November 01; UP029.004883
    LXXVIII,39
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 November 04; UP029.040.080.00030 (Box 80, Folder 30)
    LXXVIII,40
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 November 05; UP029.040.080.00031 (Box 80, Folder 31)
    LXXVIII,41
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 November 06; UP029.040.080.00032 (Box 80, Folder 32)
    LXXVIII,42
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 November 07; UP029.040.080.00033 (Box 80, Folder 33)
    LXXVIII,43
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 November 08; UP029.004884
    LXXVIII,44
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 November 12; UP029.004885
    LXXVIII,45
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 November 13; UP029.004886
    LXXVIII,46
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 November 14; UP029.004887
    LXXVIII,47
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 November 15; UP029.004888
    LXXVIII,48
    There are two PDFs for this issue. The first one represents pages one and two, and the second one represents pages three through six.
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 November 18; UP029.004889
    LXXVIII,49
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 November 19; UP029.004890
    LXXVIII,50
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 November 20; UP029.004891
    LXXVIII,51
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 November 21; UP029.004892
    LXXVIII,52
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 November 22; UP029.004893
    LXXVIII,53
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 November 25; UP029.004894
    LXXVIII,54
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 November 26; UP029.004895
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 December 02; UP029.004896
    LXXVIII,55
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 December 03; UP029.004897
    LXXVIII,57
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 December 04; UP029.004898
    LXXVIII,58
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 December 05; UP029.004899
    LXXVIII,59
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 December 06; UP029.004900
    LXXVIII,60
  - Tufts Daily, 2019 December 09; UP029.004901
    LXXVIII,61
- Tufts Daily, 2020; UP029.041; 95 Digital Object(s); 1.64 Gigabytes
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 January 16; UP029.041.081.00001
    LXXIX,1
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 January 22; UP029.041.081.00002 (Box 81)
    LXXIX,2
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 January 24; UP029.041.081.00003
    LXXIX,3
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 January 28; UP029.041.081.00004
    LXXIX,4
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 January 30; UP029.004923 (Box 81)
    Volume, Issue
    LXXIX, 5
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 February 03; UP029.041.081.00005 (Box 81)
    LXXIX,6
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 February 04; UP029.041.081.00006
    LXXIX,XI
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 February 05; UP029.041.081.00007
    LXXIX,8
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 February 06; UP029.041.081.00008
    LXXIX,9
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 February 07; UP029.041.081.00009
    LXXIX,10
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 February 10; UP029.041.081.00010
    LXXIX,12
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 February 11; UP029.041.081.00011
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 February 12; UP029.041.081.00012
    LXXIX,13
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 February 13; UP029.041.081.00013
    LXXIX,14
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 February 14; UP029.041.081.00014
    LXXIX,15
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 February 18; UP029.041.081.00015
    LXXIX,16
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 February 19; UP029.041.081.00016
    LXXIX,17
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 February 20; UP029.041.081.00017
    LXXIX,18
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 February 21; UP029.041.081.00018
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 February 24; UP029.041.081.00019
    LXXIX,20
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 February 25; UP029.041.081.00020
    LXXIX,21
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 February 26; UP029.041.081.00021
    LXXIX,22
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 February 27; UP029.041.081.00022
    LXXIX,23
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 February 28; UP029.041.081.00023 (Box 81)
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 March 02; UP029.041.081.00024
    LXXIX,24
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 March 03; UP029.041.081.00025
    LXXIX,25
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 March 04; UP029.041.081.00026
    LXXIX,27
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 March 06; UP029.041.081.00027
    LXXIX,28
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 March 09; UP029.041.081.00028
    LXXIX,30
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 March 10; UP029.041.081.00029
    LXXIX,31
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 March 11; UP029.041.081.00030
    LXXIX,32
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 March 12; UP029.041.081.00031
    LXXIX,33
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 March 30; UP029.041.081.00032
    LXXIX,34
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 April 05; UP029.041.081.00033
    LXXIX,35
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 April 13; UP029.041.081.00034
    LXXIX,36
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 April 19; UP029.041.081.00035
    LXXIX,37
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 April 28; UP029.041.081.00036
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 May 17; UP029.041.081.00037
    LXXIX,39
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 September 08; UP029.041.081.00038 (Box 81)
    LXXX,1
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 September 10; UP029.041.081.00039
    LXXX,2
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 September 14; UP029.041.081.00040 (Box 81)
    LXXX,3
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 September 16; UP029.041.081.00041
    LXXX,4
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 September 18; UP029.041.081.00042
    LXXX,5
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 September 21; UP029.041.081.00043 (Box 81)
    LXXX,6
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 September 23; UP029.041.081.00044
    LXXX,7
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 September 25; UP029.041.081.00045
    LXXX,8
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 September 28; UP029.041.081.00046 (Box 81)
    LXXX,9
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 September 29; UP029.041.081.00047
    LXXX,10
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 September 30; UP029.041.081.00048
    LXXX,11
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 October 01; UP029.041.081.00049
    LXXX,12
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 October 02; UP029.041.081.00050
    LXXX,13
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 October 05; UP029.041.081.00051 (Box 81)
    LXXX,14
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 October 06; UP029.041.081.00052
    LXXX,15
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 October 07; UP029.041.081.00053
    LXXX,16
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 October 08; UP029.041.081.00054
    LXXX,17
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 October 09; UP029.041.081.00055
    LXXX,18
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 October 12; UP029.041.081.00056 (Box 81)
    LXXX,19
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 October 13; UP029.041.081.00057
    LXXX,20
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 October 14; UP029.041.081.00058
    LXXX,21
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 October 15; UP029.041.081.00059
    LXXX,22
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 October 16; UP029.041.081.00060
    LXXX,23
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 October 19; UP029.041.081.00061 (Box 81)
    LXXX,24
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 October 20; UP029.041.081.00062
    LXXX,25
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 October 21; UP029.041.081.00063
    LXXX,26
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 October 22; UP029.041.081.00064
    LXXX,27
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 October 23; UP029.041.081.00065
    LXXX,28
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 October 26; UP029.041.081.00066 (Box 81)
    LXXX,29
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 October 27; UP029.041.081.00067
    LXXX,30
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 October 28; UP029.041.081.00068
    LXXX,31
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 October 29; UP029.041.081.00069
    LXXX,32
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 October 31; UP029.041.081.00070
    XXX,Daddy Issues
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 November 03; UP029.041.081.00071 (Box 81)
    LXXX,34
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 November 04; UP029.041.081.00072
    LXXX,35
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 November 05; UP029.041.081.00073
    LXXX,36
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 November 06; UP029.041.081.00074
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 November 09; UP029.041.081.00075
    LXXX,37
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 November 10; UP029.041.081.00076
    LXXX,38
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 November 12; UP029.041.081.00077
    LXXX,39
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 November 13; UP029.041.081.00078
    LXXX,40
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 November 16; UP029.041.081.00079
    LXXX,41
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 November 17; UP029.041.081.00080
    LXXX,42
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 November 18; UP029.041.081.00081
    LXXX,43
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 November 19; UP029.041.081.00082
    LXXX,44
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 November 20; UP029.041.081.00083
    LXXX,45
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 November 23; UP029.041.081.00084
    LXXX,46
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 November 24; UP029.041.081.00085
    LXXX,47
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 November 30; UP029.041.081.00086
    LXXX,48
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 December 01; UP029.041.081.00087
    LXXX,49
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 December 02; UP029.041.081.00088
    LXXX,50
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 December 03; UP029.041.081.00089
    LXXX,51
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 December 04; UP029.041.081.00090
    LXXX,52
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 December 07; UP029.041.081.00091
    LXXX,53
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 December 08; UP029.041.081.00092
    LXXX,54
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 December 09; UP029.041.081.00093
    LXXX,55
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 December 10; UP029.041.081.00094
    LXXX,56
  - Tufts Daily, 2020 December 11; UP029.041.081.00095
    LXXX,57
- Tufts Daily, 2021; UP029.042; 52 Digital Object(s); 365 Megabytes
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 February 01; UP029.042.082.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.16 Megabytes (Box 81)
    LXXXI,1
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 February 03; UP029.042.082.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.21 Megabytes
    LXXXI,2
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 February 05; UP029.042.082.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.77 Megabytes
    LXXXI,3
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 February 08; UP029.042.082.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.57 Megabytes
    LXXXI,4
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 February 10; UP029.042.082.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 2.38 Megabytes
    LXXXI,5
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 February 16; UP029.042.082.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 2.66 Megabytes
    LXXXI,7
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 February 18; UP029.042.082.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.17 Megabytes
    LXXXI,8
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 February 22; UP029.042.082.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.86 Megabytes
    LXXXI,9
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 February 23; UP029.042.082.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.67 Megabytes
    LXXXI,10
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 February 24; UP029.042.082.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.65 Megabytes
    LXXXI,11
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 February 25; UP029.042.082.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.27 Megabytes (Box 81)
    LXXXI,12
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 February 26; UP029.042.082.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.9 Megabytes
    LXXXI,13
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 March 01; UP029.042.082.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.23 Megabytes
    LXXXI,14
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 March 02; UP029.042.082.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 2.74 Megabytes
    LXXXI,15
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 March 03; UP029.042.082.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 3.06 Megabytes
    LXXXI,16
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 March 04; UP029.042.082.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.31 Megabytes
    LXXXI,17
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 March 05; UP029.042.082.00022
    LXXXI,18
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 March 08; UP029.042.082.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 10.55 Megabytes
    LXXXI,19
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 March 09; UP029.042.082.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.48 Megabytes
    LXXXI,20
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 March 10; UP029.042.082.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.97 Megabytes
    LXXXI,21
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 March 11; UP029.042.082.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.38 Megabytes
    LXXXI,22
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 March 12; UP029.042.082.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.37 Megabytes
    LXXXI,23
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 March 15; UP029.042.082.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.12 Megabytes (Box 81)
    LXXXI,24
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 March 16; UP029.042.082.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.47 Megabytes
    LXXXI,25
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 March 17; UP029.042.082.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.24 Megabytes
    LXXXI,26
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 March 18; UP029.042.082.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.15 Megabytes
    LXXXI,27
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 March 19; UP029.042.082.00031; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.42 Megabytes
    LXXXI,28
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 March 22; UP029.042.082.00032; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.42 Megabytes
    LXXXI,29
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 March 23; UP029.042.082.00033; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.18 Megabytes
    LXXXI,30
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 March 24; UP029.042.082.00034; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.04 Megabytes
    LXXXI,31
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 March 25; UP029.042.082.00035
    LXXXI,32
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 March 30; UP029.042.082.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.24 Megabytes (Box 81)
    LXXXI,33
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 March 31; UP029.042.082.00036; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.24 Megabytes
    LXXXI,34
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 April 02; UP029.042.082.00037; 1 Digital Object(s); 3.32 Megabytes
    LXXXI,35
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 April 05; UP029.042.082.00038; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.23 Megabytes
    LXXXI,36
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 April 06; UP029.042.082.00039; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.83 Megabytes
    LXXXI,37
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 April 07; UP029.042.082.00040; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.42 Megabytes
    LXXXI,38
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 April 08; UP029.042.082.00041; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.8 Megabytes
    LXXXI,39
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 April 09; UP029.042.082.00042; 1 Digital Object(s); 3.88 Megabytes
    LXXXI,40
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 April 12; UP029.042.082.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.79 Megabytes (Box 81)
    LXXXI,41
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 April 14; UP029.042.082.00043; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.39 Megabytes
    LXXXI,42
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 April 15; UP029.042.082.00044; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.71 Megabytes
    LXXXI,43
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 April 16; UP029.042.082.00045; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.51 Megabytes
    LXXXI,44
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 April 20; UP029.042.082.00046; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.41 Megabytes
    LXXXI,45
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 April 21; UP029.042.082.00047; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.29 Megabytes
    LXXXI,46
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 April 22; UP029.042.082.00048; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.76 Megabytes
    LXXXI,47
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 April 23; UP029.042.082.00049; 1 Digital Object(s); 3.67 Megabytes
    LXXXI,48
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 April 26; UP029.042.082.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.05 Megabytes (Box 81)
    LXXXI,49
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 April 28; UP029.042.082.00050; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.05 Megabytes
    LXXXI,50
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 May 03; UP029.042.082.00051; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.95 Megabytes
    LXXXI,51
  - Tufts Daily, 2021 May 05; UP029.042.082.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 36.08 Megabytes (Box 81)
    LXXXI,53